Visit turkision.com for more!
Brother, stop!
Stop! Alaaddin
-Leave him! Leave him!
-Get back!
Brother! Brother!
You are a dead man, Alaaddin.
Who could save you now?
Brother!
-Gonca? Gonca!
-Gonca?
-Gonca? Gonca.
-Leave her!
Leave my sister!
-Gonca.
-Gonca, are you alright?
I'm good.
This is because of you!
Enough! Enough!
Brother, stop already!
He doesn't see what he did and still blames me!
Hasan, bring the bag!
We need to wrap the wound!
Gokmen!
Let him bring it.
-Are you alright?
-I'm good.
Get your hand off!
Give it to me.
Come to me. Let me wrap it.
Know your place, Alaaddin.
Know your place! Otherwise
I will have to kill you!
Wait, Gonca.
My Shahzade, Gorklu Khan
is advancing to Yenisehir.
What are you saying?
Alps!
Get on horses!
'm good. Just go.
Please.
We're going to Yenisehir!
Alaaddin!
I owed you a life.
So I spared your life.
I'll show no mercy anymore!
With a tiny mistake of
yours, I will take your life.
It's only Allah Who takes
and gives lives, Mehmed Bey.
I stopped for Gonca's sake.
But next time
...I will show no mercy.
Let's go!
While you are dying here, Gorklu
Khan is burning Yenisehir down.
We're destroying you from all directions, Osman!
Soldiers of Kayi!
Get up!
It is...
It's the day of reckoning today!
You will pay for every life you harm
-Allah is the greatest!
-Nokers.
Leave nobody alive!
All the accounts will be settled today!
-Come on, alps!
-Allah is the greatest!
Alps! Stop them!
Break their hopes! Come on!
We won't let them get inside the palace!
Mongolian dog Gorklu Khan!
Yenisehir will be your death!
You will never get the princess!
Yenisehir will burn to ashes...
...with my wrath.
Kill everyone!
Nokers search the dungeon. There is nobody.
Princess must be in Osman's palace.
Go there.
Find her.
-Bala!
-Close the doors, alps!
Close the doors!
You're trying in vain, Osman.
I will kill you and take my revenge.
These lands where you came for revenge...
..will be your death.
You'll take revenge?
Who are you to take revenge from me?
Allah is the greatest!
Who are you? Where did you come from?
As long as you attack the innocent,
...you will see us all against you.
Nokers, we were to hold Osman and we did!
Get back!
You're running off again!
Uraz Bey.
-Are you alright?
-Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
Alps, check the wounded.
Put out all the fires.
My Bey we can handle here.
You go to the city. For
the sake of State of Osman.
Do not worry. In the end..
..in the end we will be victorious.
I swear we will.
Come on alps.
We're heading to Yenisehir.
Come on hurry! We will strike them from behind!
We will show them Yenisehir is not unguarded!
Come on.
Tong Chu, leave my most skilled soldier here.
Osman will come after me.
He will report his every move.
As you command Emir Gorklu Khan
Burn it all!
If we fall, Yenisehir will fall! Hold on!
Hold the doors! Hold them!
Hold on!
The Righteous!
Yenisehir was made home with martyr blood!
You will know not to pass from these lands!
Nokers are nearing the palace!
The lines of defence are broken!
They're at the doors, come on!
-Bala! Bala!
-Come on.
Alps hold on!
We're holding the palace!
To the passages! Come on!
Break the door!
-Come on!
-Take positions!
-To arms!
-Come on!
Come on! With haste!
Alps, hold the door!
-Come on!
-There are no more places to defend!
Now it is time to attack!
You won't have Yenisehir
without getting past me first!
Alps, come on to the doors!
Hold each place! Do not give up!
Come on!
This city..
..will burn with my wrath!
I will take both your brave
hearts and the princess!
Get ready.
Now!
You dogs!
Drown them with arrows!
The Righteous!
Attack valiants!
We will banish these dogs from Yenisehir!
Allah is the greatest! Come on!
I will turn these lands into hell..
..until I get the princess!
Tell that to Osman!
The Righteous!
Bring ladders! Climb the walls!
Come, you dogs!
Come you dogs!
Protect Fatma!
Nokers! We are done here!
Fall back!
Not even one noker will leave here alive!
Attack! Allah is the greatest!
Are you alright my daughter?
-I am alright mother.
You will be alright. You are
your moms strong daughter.
Orhan.
Thank Allah. You came right in time, son.
Sister, are you alright?
It's nothing, brother.
-Are you alright?
We're alright. Come on to the healer.
Send word to the healers.
Carry every wounded to the healers!
Alps, build defences on the
marketplace exit, we won't let them in!
Alps, put out the fires.
Come on! Tend to the wounded!
Do not worry, we will be alright.
We will be alright.
They burned down Yenisehir.
They burned down everywhere.
Inna Lillahi Wa Inna Ilayhi Raji'un
Gorklu Khan.
You burned down my Yenisehir.
You did this to my people.
You., you..
Only one day.
When sun conies up, I will have you pay for this!
I will have your head and give it to my people!
As long as I am Osman Bey.
Alps! Gather around!
Come on!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Mother..
Are you going to sacrifice
your life for that man?
Did you lose your mind, Gonca?
My brother would have killed Alaeddin
if I had not stood before him!
Let him!
Why do you care?
Since when do you love him
enough to sacrifice your own life?
I won't allow that, Gonca!
I will not allow that!
What is it that you will not allow, huh?
Didn't you drag me into this game?
Did you just realize what you did, mother?
I gave you a duty!
I told you to make him fall in love with you!
I told you to burn Alaeddin!
But you burnt yourself, my daughter!
Gonca... look, my daughter.
Look... I am your mother, Gonca!
Did you remember your motherhood?
I will not sacrifice you for this love.
I will not let that happen. You will
not see Alaeddin anymore, Gonca!
You will not see Alaeddin!
Gonca!
Are you alright, my daughter?
I am alright, father. How did this happen?
Who attacked you?
It's not important, father.
When we were after the
Princess, some of the Alps...
What were you doing there, Mehmet?
Didn't I give you another duty?
Why do you say that, my Bey?
He was fortunately there. He arrived on time.
Anyway.
Now, let's talk about the actual issue.
Gorklu Khan raided Yenisehir.
Osman made a huge mistake...
...by taking that Princess captive.
The marketplace of Yenisehir was destroyed.
Now it cannot be repaired, huh, my father?
Right... right. Osman's marketplace...
...and his dreams of a state were destroyed.
With this move...
...they were all destroyed.
Father..
Are you happy about this?
What about all the lives we lost?
Don't you feel sorry for
those innocent people, father?
How can you say that, Gonca?
Do you think I am not in pain?
They were our people, they were our family.
But... wasn't it Osman's duty...
...to protect his people?
I don't feel sorry for Osman.
I feel sorry for his people who are crushed..
...under his dreams.
Now, we will protect Kayi's..
...people.
We will protect what Osman could not protect.
Come on. Get ready.
We will go and give them our warm wishes.
Father...
Gonca must stay here.
She is injured.
-Thank you, brother.
But it is a scratch.
I am alright. I will come.
Good then. Come on.
We will be alright. -Father!
Fatma...
What is this?
A scratch, father. I am alright.
Of my veteran daughter...
What is the situation?
The fact that Orhan arrived on time
reduced the number of losses, my Bey.
Thanks to Allah..
But still, we have a lot to do.
We must reconstruct Yenisehir.
We will.
Of course we will.
I will make those...
...who did this to my people...
...to my Alps...
...pay the price so heavily that, I swear...
...I swear..
...I know...
I know what to do to that dog.
Now it's time.
Emir Hadhrat.
You set the biggest trap.
For Osman's head..
Don't you also want that?
I want his head!
I want to rule Yenisehir...
...and Bilecik after Osman dies.
If Emir Hadhrat allows..
You chose the right side, Lord.
You will get the things you want.
Now go. Prepare your soldiers.
We will kill them all.
You stopped us for no reason, Bala Hatun!
If we went to the frontiers marketplace...
...our goods would not be damaged.
Your lives and goods were entrusted to us.
We are the ones who suffer the most.
All of your lost goods will
be covered. Don't worry.
We want to go to the frontiers marketplace!
People!
Today is the day of unity.
If we don't unite, we will be ruined
Bala Hatun is right.
They raid wherever we go.
We should not go.
Yenisehir is entrusted to us!
We are not going anywhere!
We are here! We will stay here!
Those who want to stay may stay...
But we are going to the
frontiers marketplace. Come on.
Get well soon, the people of Yenisehir!
We came to share your sorrow!
Are the doors of the frontiers
marketplace still open for us, Yakup Bey?
Always, always.
Attention! Osman Bey!
My Bey, all of our Alps are ready...
...to go after Gorklu Khan.
Even the injured ones want to join.
Trackers are on the way.
We will soon find out where they went.
If we hurry, we can catch them, my Bey.
We must not come back before
we take that dog's head, my Bey!
Revenge is a must now!
Karaali.
-My Shahzade.
Tell the Alps to get ready.
We will go after Gorklu Khan.
We will not hit Gorklu Khan.
He is expecting us to chase him.
Now is not the time.
For what, father?
That dastard hurt us.
He will not get away with this.
We will go there.
You will do as I say!
My Bey, how will people trust
us if we don't go after this dog?
If we don't cut his head
If we don't punish him for this...
-Enough!
It's not enough, my Bey!
Go away!
Get out of here!
You have no place here anymore.
Okay, father.
If there is no battle
then there is no need for a sword.
Goodbye.
You tricked people for no reason.
It wouldn't have happened like
this if you hadn't took people...
...away from the Frontier marketplace.
-What do you mean, Saadet Hatun?
Are Mongols our enemy alone?
Are they not your enemies too?
How do you know they will not
attack the frontier marketplace?
You are the ones who provoked Mongols,
and people are suffering from it.
If you hadn't kidnapped the Princess,
they wouldn't have attacked Yenisehir.
If Princess had married Gorklu Khan
Byzantines and Mongols
would have made an alliance.
Not only us, you will be crushed as well.
Do not turn a blind eye to the truth.
You're the only ones who
know the truth, is that so?
Orhan?
What happened, son? Where
are you going without your sword?
I have no sword to swing for Osman Bey anymore.
Your son is so furious.
But his fury will burn him first.
It is not your place to talk about my son.
No, it is.
Your children exceed the limits way too much.
Now, they hurt themselves.
But if they don't learn their lessons,
and if they make mistakes again
then they have no lives to hurt.
Are you threatening us?
Osman Bey, you dismissed your child
but he's telling the truth.
You have the option to give
the Princess and get rid of it,
but you're choosing the hard way.
Never.
-Never.
-Osman Bey.
You're not the only one in pain.
The whole community is suffering.
You're putting these people in danger.
No.
I will not let you turn our lands into hell.
Yakup Bey.
I'll do whatever it takes to
protect this heavenly lands.
If I need to go to hell for this
I'll go there too.
You will give the Princess, Osman Bey.
Enough.
Yakup Bey.
If we give the Princess
then we will suffer ten times more than this.
Can you still not see it?
Of course we will have
hardships and we will be beaten.
But
otherwise
then we will disappear.
What do you think will happen?
How are they going to destroy us?
Yakup Bey.
How did they collapse the state of Seljuks
and took away
what they ruled?
It was not enough for them.
They will designate it as their headquarters
and they will move towards the west.
I'll stand against them.
I will be their first target.
But if they surpass me
then they will come to you.
First they will make you pay taxes.
But
if you don't make another deal with them.
It will not be enough.
Whatever they did to Konya,
they will do the same to Kutahya.
They will put a governor over you.
They will destroy Karesi and Candar
and then it will be your turn.
Then they will destroy you.
This is why Byzantine gave the Princess.
To delay things.
There's no need to switch plans.
You cannot hide the Princess forever, Osman.
-Gorklu Khan will find her...
-Don't worry.
Gorklu Khan cannot hide from my sword forever.
It is time.
Osman!
My Bey, Orhan...
If you'll excuse us, Yakup Bey...
Sure, Osman Bey.
Think about what I've said.
Osman, Orhan was leaving without his sword.
Crusaders and Mongols are
waiting for an opportunity to attack us.
What if something happens again?
What if they set traps?
He will suffer what's will happen to him.
This was his decision.
Don't worry.
My Sultan, Gorklu Khan's men...
Keep me informed about it.
Yes, my Sultan.
You wait.
What does Osman think? Why
hasn't he gone after Gorklu Khan?
Osman is worried a lot. The attack on Yenisehir...
...feels heavy for him.
He crushed his Shahzade Orhan
because he wanted revenge.
It will take time for him to gain strength.
Gorklu Khan will soon crush him.
What about the Princess? Where is she?
We couldn't find her yet.
Osman is keeping her place as a secret.
Tell Yakup who sees himself as Sultan,
that if he cannot find the
Princess in the lands he rules...
...his end is clear...
...we will kill him before Osman.
People are going to the
Frontier marketplace, Yakup Bey.
Orhan stood up to Osman.
He left.
Osman's household is ruining, Hatun.
First Orhan, and then the others.
Everyone will see the truth.
Very well.
Come on.
-We're setting out.
-Shut the gates!
What's going on, Alaeddin Bey?
By the order of Osman Bey...
Entrances and exits to
Yenisehir have been blocked.
What are you saying, Alaeddin?
Open the gate, we will leave.
On what grounds are you keeping us here?
There is a traitor inside.
No one will leave Yenisehir before we find him.
Why would I care about your traitor?
Open the gates, we will leave.
It is the order of Osman Bey.
I will not let anyone disobey my Bey.
Nobody will leave Yenisehir, Yakup Bey.
I will crush you first..
...and then your Bey's order, Alaaddin.
I say we'll get out.
Open the gates.
Alps!
You will pay for this, Osman.
We're going to the palace.
What's going on, Ulgen?
I don't know.
-Speak quickly.
-I swear I don't know.
-Did you tell them anything?
-No.
You won't say a word.
Neither you nor Cerkutay...
...will say a single word.
Did you hear me?
I did. I won't talk to anyone.
If you care about your son
...you won't talk.
If you two say a single word,
...first your son and then you two..
Don't make me say the rest, Ulgen.
Come on.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in.
My Bey, Yakup Bey wants to see you.
Who are you..
...not to let me leave the city?
This is a cause of war, Osman.
Yakup Bey.
You always want to fight those on your own side.
Why are you holding me here?
Not only you.
I'm holding everyone here.
All the gates of the city have been closed.
Why?
There is a traitor in my city.
Then find the traitor, Osman Bey.
How could you hold the sultan?
Are you blaming me?
No.
No, Yakup Bey.
Just the opposite.
I'm protecting you.
We should find the traitor...
...and find out who he is working
for and who he is trying to harm.
You will be my guests here until then.
When we find out who he intends to harm,
...you can leave.
If you are hurt somehow
...things will be much crazier and chaotic.
And I will never let that happen.
Nobody can hurt me.
You are the reason of this chaos.
This is the last time...
...I'm forgiving your impertinence, Osman.
For your information!
Whoever has even a small part in this issue,
...I won't forgive them.
For your information.
Yakup Bey.
Where are you, Cerkutay?
You've ruined us.
Ulgen, what's going on?
Cerkutay. Saadet...
Saadet crossed my path and threatened me.
"If you are going to speak, I
will kill Ghazi and you", she said.
What will we do now, Cerkutay?
Don't be afraid, my Ulgen.
Nobody...
...can hurt our son even slightly.
But...
We need to send Ghazi away for a while.
How will we get out of this hell?
Ulgen.
Go prepare Ghazi's bag.
I will figure something out.
I will.
I will, Ulgen.
-I will.
-Mother! Mother!
Is Gonca Hatun in Yenisehir? Did I hear right?
My boy.
My boy. My son.
Now...
...forget about Gonca Hatun.
Your mother is preparing your bag.
You'll be a guest somewhere else for a while.
I'm not going anywhere! Gonca Hatun is here.
I will stay here!
Ghazi. Cerkutay...
Then I need to give the duty to another alp.
Duty?
Things will change then.
Yes, duty.
Duty awaits you, Ghazi Alp.
What will we do, father?
Just wait here?
-Let me burn this palace down. -Mehmed!
Shut up!
Osman is mad.
He will let nobody leave the
city before he finds the traitor.
If Cerkutay speaks
If our plan we made on the beys is revealed,
...my reputation will be ruined.
We can't gather the beys behind us again.
Cerkutay will not speak.
Don't worry, son.
He won't speak.
I threatened Ulgen.
If they care about their son
...neither of them will speak.
Sorry?
What did you do?
I did the right thing, Gonca.
You should do the right thing at the right time.
It's not time for mercy now.
-Is it right to threatening
a mother with her son?
Gonca!
Enough, Gonca!
Enough!
There is no right or wrong anymore!
All the beys stand beside us with threats.
Did you forget that?
If Cerkutay speaks
...we will remain alone and be destroyed.
Enough!
Gonca.
Your mother just intimidated her.
Well done, hatun.
We have just a few alps here.
If Cerkutay speaks
...none of us can get out of
this palace alive, my daughter.
Cerkutay won't speak...
..no matter what.
We have a strong ally against Osman, Olivia.
Gorklu Khan.
Gorklu Khan will make us stronger.
But... Osman.
He's unpredictable.
Gorklu Khan has a spy in Yenisehir, Olivia.
We will know about their every step.
Osman has worn out after the attack on Yenisehir.
He kicked his son Orhan out of his palace.
There will be nobody around him soon.
Good.
Just as we want.
Osman is getting lonelier.
What is our next move?
Osman will go after Gorklu Khan to take revenge.
And he will face an unprecedented trap there.
While Osman and his armies are...
...trying to find Gorklu Khan,
...my armies will get them into a death circle.
Good. We just need to find Princess Maria now.
Lord Leon.
Speak, soldier.
Our watchmen around the castle...
...have been knocked out and tied to a tree.
One of them was stripped. There is a spy inside.
Do you hear what you are saying, soldier?
What are you waiting for? Catch the spy! Orhan!
Catch him, soldiers.
Lord Leon, I'm not here to fight but talk to you.
You infiltrated into my castle.
You will pay the price! Catch him, soldiers!
Tell them to put their swords down!
What are you waiting for, soldiers? Catch him!
What is it Andra? Did you learn anything?
Did Orhan go back to Kestel?
Osman Bey.
Took Kestel and Beylik from Shahzade Orhan.
Because of him kidnapping you.
Because of me.
It is because of me.
I will get away, Andra.
This visit is an opportunity.
My Lady, your aunt will be very mad.
I do not care.
I do not care Andra. Orhan
gave up on everything for me.
-I will go to him.
-Look everywhere!
Shahzade Orhan is here!
What is Orhan doing here?
Andra if Orhan gets caught, it will be very bad.
We need to help him.
Let us go.
Come on.
Soldiers, catch him!
Stop! My intention is to only speak!
Catch him, now!
Let go!
I called you my blood brother!
-Does it fit you, what you did Cerkutay?
-Don't!
I did not do it!
I didn't do anything!
To whom did you send word with this bird?
To whom are you spy to?
Don't do it, Boran Bey. Let him go.
We let him go when he wanted, Sister Ulgen.
But he came back to betray us.
He came back to strike our hearts with a dagger.
He didn't do anything.
-I didn't do anything!
-I didn't do it! -He will pay for it.
Alps! Take him to the court now!
Send word to my Osman Bey.
-Quickly!
-Move! Come on!
-Move!
-Don't do it!
-Let him go, please!
We've found the traitor in the palace.
There are noises outside. What is it?
We will find out now.
Kanyumaz.
My Sultan.
What is happening?
They say Osman Bey has
found the traitor, my Sultan.
They're heading to the court.
Did they find about Cerkutay?
Don't speak ill, Gonca.
May Allah prevent it.
Come on.
Father.
Cerkutay.
Has been exposed.
Alps caught him.
Come on!
Bring him up.
I will not stop beating you..
..until you tell me who the traitor is.
Bring him up.
Cerkutay.
I've known you as my alp. I
walked to many wars with you.
How many alps have been killed because of you.
Don't you pity?
How did you sell us out?
Whoever it is that you've
been informing with that pigeon..
..I will have you both
hanged at the walls of this city.
-I did not betray you.
-Shut it.
I gave you property..
gave you power..
..how can you do this to me?
I told myself; "Cerkutay
won't sell himself for gold."
"Cerkutay won't sell himself for money."
How can you do this? How?
Did they threaten you with your family?
Did they threaten you with your dynasty?
If I'd known..
..I would've killed you the moment I met you.
However..
..you've changed a lot,
being a prisoner for years..
..but I couldn't notice it.
Take him to prison.
You will continue beating him..
..until he tells us who the traitor is.
We will keep hurting him..
..until he tells the truth.
I will personally..
..skin him myself.
-Take him.
-As you command, my Bey.
Move.
Cerkutay didn't speak, however..
..if he does, everything will be in danger.
Including our lives.
Osman went completely mad.
What will we do, father?
Send word to Candar and..
..Karasid Beys in secrecy.
Tell them to bring the armies.
To siege Yenisehir.
You didn't leave me any choice.
You're playing with fire, Shahzade Orhan.
You will pay for it.
You can not leave here alive.
Let go of Olivia.
Orhan.
What are you doing?
I will tell you soon.
I will tell you all, Holofira.
Lord, you've seen it with your own eyes.
I didn't kill a single soldier of yours.
I didn't come here as an enemy.
My intention is to provide peace.
By sneaking into my castle and spying around?
We will find a mutual way
and you will listen, Lord.
Don't you want Princess Maria?
I will give you her.
How will you do that?
Despite your father?
How can we trust you?
The arrogance of Osman Bey..
..destroyed Yenisehir!
He took my beylik, my castle from me..
..on top of not admitting his own mistakes!
Osman Bey..
..took my father from me.
Orhan.
Princess Maria.
Brought nothing but trouble to us.
I will hand her over to you..
..and provide peace to my people.
I will do this..
..even if it means..
..dying by my father's hands.
It is your decision now.
Shahzade Orhan.
Tomorrow, you will bring
the Princess with my soldiers.
Do not worry, Lord.
We both will get what we want.
Fatma... Where are we going? My
brother always keeps an eye on me.
I informed the Sisters.
They will let us know if he comes.
I... wanted you to see Ghazi.
You did well.
Ghazi Alp. -Gonca Hatun!
My Gonca Hatun!
Gonca Hatun... They did
not let me leave the kitchen!
My mother gets jealous when I want to see you!
Look at him...
Let me look at you.
-You grew up a little.
-Really?
I grew up, right?
I am old enough to get
married, right, Gonca Hatun?
But...
Ooo, Ghazi Alp...
You are also here, huh?
Why did you come, Shahzade?
Do not come between us!
I saw Gonca Hatun first!
I loved her first!
No, you are wrong.
I was the first one to see and love her.
Is he telling the truth?
Yes, what can we do?
He was the first one to see me.
Then... we are unfortunate today.
What am I going to do now, huh?
But, no... No, Gonca Hatun!
You don't love this Shahzade!
Is that so? -Yes!
Ghazi... Come on.
Come on, come.
Gonca Hatun, you do
not love him! You don't!
Come on!
Look at him..
Alaeddin...
What happened?
I don't understand! It is all too complicated!
I don't know, Gonca.
How are you? How is your wound? Is it better now?
I am alright.
I was afraid that something would happen to you.
Don't be scared.
But... promise me.
You will not do what you did today again.
You will not risk your own
life to protect me, Gonca.
No...
You cannot ask this from me, Alaeddin.
I owe you a lot.
Gonca..
You don't owe me anything.
Your life has become my life.
Do not hurt it any more while trying to save it.
Gazelle-eyed Hatun.
Can I come in, my Shahzade?
Come in.
My Shahzade...
Osman Bey is waiting for you.
I am coming, Ulgen Hatun.
I am leaving. -Alright.
How are we going to tell
this to Alaeddin, my Osman?
You are right, my Bala...
You are right, but..
We need to tell him.
My Alaeddin Ali is strong.
He can get over this.
Right... But it will be hard.
It will be too hard.
When have we ever faced something easy?
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in...
Father...
We have something to tell you.
Father, what is going on?
How is Cerkutay Bey a traitor?
We have other things to tell you...
...and also, we have that issue about Cerkutay.
My son.
The issue is about Yakup Bey..
...and Gonca.
Gonca?
They knew that we would take Karacelasun...
...from the inn...
...because Gonca told them.
She approached you because
her mother told her to do it.
My son.
I know that it is hard.
It is really hard.
But you will stay strong.
It was all a game, huh?
Would someone sacrifice
her life for a game, father?
Son.
It is not about Gonca only.
Yakup Bey is trying to trick
us at every opportunity he gets.
So,
we don't know who to trust.
We need to be careful.
We will not trust, father.
We will not.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come on in.
My Bey, I've sent Ghazi.
Do not let him see his father in that state.
We will have to suffer.
Shame on you!
Calm down, it will be over.
Father.
We need to shoot Cerkutay.
No.
I will not kill the soldier
who bows to the sword,
I applaud him.
Whoever betrays the hand that feeds him
is killed by the same hand
Everything will be revealed, including
who do you work for and what did you do.
But you will not live until then.
My Bey.
We have news from the scouts,
Gorklu Khan's place has been discovered.
Gorklu Khan went to the frontier
marketplace and met Yakup Bey twice,
we don't know what they are up to.
He met Yakup Bey
and attacked Yenisehir, right?
Ulgen? Are you all right?
Cerkutay
say it now.
What's he going to say?
My Bey.
I made a mistake.
Yakup Bey
forced me into spying.
What?
I didn't do it, my Bey.
I didn't say anything that
would put you in a hard spot.
I didn't, I wasted his time.
I acted like I'm spying.
But I didn't.
If it was about my life
I'm willing to die to get rid of this
but he left me no other choice.
He threatened to
kill my family, my child.
Punish me, my Bey.
But protect my family
and my child.
Just like before.
Why didn't you tell me this, Cerkutay?
They are terrible people. They
even use their own daughter.
What are you saying, Ulgen?
They threatened me too.
Gonca obeyed her parents
and spied for them.
Ulgen, I've been waiting for you to speak.
Why didn't you say it before?
Saadet threatened to kill Ghazi, Bala Hatun.
My Bey, we had no other
choice but to stay silent.
Why
didn't you say it to me somehow?
I wouldn't betray you even if they skinned me,
just like I've never done before.
But my family
my child...
Forgive me.
For your child
for your family
I will skin you.
My Bey.
What's on your mind?
With Cerkutay,
we will reveal Yakup's treason.
Orhan.
You will go to Gorklu Khan.
Bring me my horse.
Come on.
Tie him to the pole.
He will stay there until I come back.
I know what to do.
I won't waste our efforts and sultanate...
...for a worthless spy.
I hope you keep your promise, Shahzade Orhan.
I didn't give that promise for you...
...but for my own people.
It's also beneficial for me
to give the princess away.
Don't be worrying.
I'm really sorry about what happened, Orhan.
-What happened between you and your father...
-Don't.
Don't be sorry.
Always smile, Lord's daughter.
You know what?
I would risk everything for you.
I was going to run away.
And come to you.
But I came to you.
You did.
-Orhan.
-Go ahead.
Even if...
...you aren't a bey
Even if you don't own a land
...my heart...
...belongs to you.
Don't you forget that, alright?
Mine too.
My heart always belong to you.
And it will always be so, Lord's daughter.
Holofira.
Shahzade Orhan is in a hurry.
Stay safe.
I've found the princess!
How?
Osman's son Orhan came to me.
He's uncomfortable with his father's moves.
He wants to give the princess away
and close the matter.
The bigger matter will begin...
...after we take the princess.
-Where?
-They keep her in a house in Gokpinar.
Orhan is going there with my soldiers.
He doesn't even have a sword.
It's from our spy in Yenisehir.
Osman is coming with his army.
Osman is coming here.
With Karacelasun...
...you will take his head!
I'm going to take the princess.
If Osman survives
...you will die!
Tajeddin Noyan.. Before he comes
...we will take care of this matter.
Otherwise, Tajeddin Noyan...
...will take care of us.
Let's go!
We'll find you!
Tell me...
...how I can get to Osman Bey's city Yenisehir.
Tell me and I spare your life.
You won't even if I tell you.
Speak!
I will find that palace eventually.
Both the enemies outside...
...and the jackals inside will be destroyed now.
Go, Mehmed. Go.
Before the arrow reaches the target,
...you will fall into my hands, Mehmed.
What's the matter, my Shahzade?
What are you doing, my Shahzade?
Don't do this.
As long as we keep the princess,
...our suffering won't end.
We have to do this Bayindir Bey.
Of course, you do.
What else can you even do against my power?
You'll get into the grave
with your secrets, Cerkutay.
We'll see if Osman can make your speak now.
You're trying to kill Cerkutay
and get away with this, huh?
The sun has risen and the
fog has cleared up, Mehmed.
Everybody will know about your betrayal!
Gonca saved you from me last time.
Who can save you now, Alaaddin?
Alaaddin!
I will take your life..
..before taking my wife.
What did you resist for?
Your father loses his life in my ambush..
..and you here, tired.
You are dead, Turk.
Osman.
Gorklu Khan.
You will neither have my son's life..
..nor your wife.
Today, death has come for you.
Bad news, Gorksuz Khan (Lowly Khan).
Today, you are prey.
And we hunters.
-Attack!
-Protect the Princess!
Come here.
Come!
We won't stop..
..until these dogs stop breathing!
You oppressed my people,
you oppressed my vassals!
Now, my anger will be upon you.
This is a war you can not win, Osman!
My end will bring yours!
The dark clouds over us will vanish when you do.
Then, we will unite!
I hear swords clashing..
..women screaming infants crying..
..nokers with torches, Osman!
They are coming for you!
Let them come!
We have enough land to bury them all!
Gorklu Khan.
I am the state..
..I am the Bey.
Son, you've achieved great. May you prosper.
Because of you, my Bey.
My heart cooled off..
..since you got this dog's head.
Come on now.
We're heading to Yenisehir.
Let us face with the traitors inside.
Come on now. Ayaz!
My Bey!
Bring this dog's head behind us.
As you command, my Bey.
Where is Osman Bey's palace?
Osman Bey's palace is at the end of the road.
However, you won't arrive there.
I will.
I will arrive at Yenisehir.
However, you will arrive at hell!
My people!
Look here.
Yakup Bey, the Princess you
were looking for everywhere..
..is here now.
Come here.
And this is another one.
Gorklu Khan.
Whom you met in secrecy..
..at your home.
What did you do, Osman?
What is it?
There will be many more heads to roll.
Many.
Do hear what you're saying, Osman Bey?
Of course I do.
My Bey. Suleyman Bey..
..and Karesid Bey are waiting
with their armies at the gates.
Now speak, Osman Bey.
No.
Not like that. Beys will also hear..
..what I will say.
Let them come.
My Bey.
If Yakup Bey
does not leave until mid-afternoon
-it was ordered to burn Yenisehir down.
-No.
I cannot promise.
Beys will come here
and they will see the whole situation.
Get up!
Get up.
I said get up!
Alaeddin. Alaeddin!
Everyone will see your true colors.
Everyone.
Move!
Osman Bey!
What are you trying to do?
How could you keep Sultan
Yakup in Yenisehir by force?
Gorklu Khan.
Osman Bey, you..
...did you kill Gorklu Khan?
Yes.
Sultan Yakup was right.
And now did you kill the Ilkhanate Emir?
You will not stop
until you ruin the whole country.
Osman Bey is still the same.
He keeps swinging his sword
without knowing what's going to happen to him?
What about you?
Do you know what's going to happen to you?
Tell me, do you know, Yakup Bey?
Move!
Let go off me! Don't touch me!
Let go off me! -Mehmed.
Brother?
Let go off me.
You've been exposed, Yakup Bey.
Mehmed Bey, son of Yakup Bey,
tried to shoot Cerkutay
when his treason is exposed.
Not only Cerkutay,
tell me,
tell me
How can
a man make his daughter a spy?
What are you saying, Osman Bey?
Here's your Hatun.
Here are your children.
They're here, ask them.
But you didn't threaten only Cerkutay.
Not only Ulgen,
not only your daughter,
tell me, Beys.
Are you staying there voluntarily?
Tell me, are you staying there voluntarily?
It was not honorable.
So you've heard about what happened, Osman Bey.
Is this true, Sultan Yakup?
Better late
than never.
The cruel Sultan
lives short.
Now.
Now, what should I do to you, Yakup Bey?
If I try to kill you
then brothers' blood will be spilled.
They will come after me for revenge.
If I embrace you
as my brother
I don't feel well about it.
Tell me Yakup Bey.
What should I do?
What would you do
if you were me.
Not a single word you've just said
is wrong.
What you say is true.
In this case, if it was me
who was holding the sword
If I were you
I would kill you
just like Gorklu Khan.
Ah, Yakup Bey.
Whatever I did,
I did it for my country...
My Sultan! Be careful!
My Sultan!
-Father! Father!
-My Sultan!
-Father!
-Who shot an arrow?
Osman! You did it!
I swear I'll kill you!
I'll kill you!
They want to make us kill our brothers.
Alps! Come on!
-Call our doctors, come on!
-Father!
-My Sultan!
-We will go to the palace.
If something happens to my man
I'll burn Yenisehir down!
-I'll burn it down!
-Let go off me.
Let go off me, I'll kill him!
I'll find that dastard!
You're arrested Mehmed.
You can't go anywhere.
I'll kill you all if something happens to him.
Come on, hurry up!
Yakup Bey!
-Come on!
-Father!
Alps, bring the horses.
The traces divide into two here.
Alps, you will go this way.
Orhan and I will go this way. Do not come
back to Yenisehir before you find the girl.
Come on! Come on Orhan.
Father, father.
Lift him, Kanyumaz.
Father, hang on.
-Hang on, father!
-Father!
-Father.
-They killed my Bey.
Open the wound first.
Stay away! I'll not let you treat my father!
Move away, we're losing time.
Our doctors will come,
no one will touch my father.
No one will touch him!
Your father is dying and you keep talking
-Yakup Bey will die until
the doctor comes, Mehmed.
Brother!
Move! Let Alaeddin check him!
He saved you, don't you remember?
We don't have any other choice!
Do you still trust them Gonca, huh?
It's a game! They did this to my father!
Baysungur!
Move! Alaeddin!
I won't let you live if something
happens to my father, I swear!
Enough, Mehmet! We are
all trying to help him survive.
If my Bey dies...
...you will pay for this, Alaeddin.
I will make you
all pay for this.
If we lose any more time he will die anyway.
Step back.
-Hang on, Yakup Bey.
-Father.
Cerkutay ran away!
My Bey...
They killed our Alps.
There might be a trap.
My son.
Stop, don't kill her!
Do not shed a Hatun's blood with my sword.
Who hired you?
You are not Mongols.
You are Kayi.
I thought you were Mongols,
that's why I drew my sword.
I wanted to take your horse and go to Osman Bey.
What are you going to do with Osman Bey?
They will kill Osman Bey
and slaughter everyone in Kayi.
Who will do that?
Tajeddin Noyan!
Tajeddin Noyan...
Hang on, father, please!
No, no... The bleeding does not stop
Alaeddin. What are we going to do?
Keep it on the wound!
Mother! Is the ointment ready?
-Almost.
Father, hang on, please!
Father, please, hang on!
My Allah, help me! -Put it in his mouth.
Alright.
Hang on, father, please! Please!
Let me see..
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate
O Healer...O Allah!
Hang on.. -Gonca, apply some of this ointment.
Alright.
Father?
Father! Father! Alaeddin!
-Yakup!
Alaeddin! My father does not breathe!
Father! -Father! Alaeddin!
Father! Father! Father!
Father!
Alaeddin, help! My father does not breathe!
Father! Father! Father!
Father! Help, please! -You took...
...my Bey from me.
And I will..
...take your lives.
Mother!
What does Ilkhanate's Sultan
Olcaytu's nephew Tajeddin Noyan...
...want from Osman Bey, huh?
He abducted the Princess of
Byzantium and announced his Beylic.
And the dogs he sent...
...could not defeat Osman Bey.
Isn't it enough?
How do you know these things?
My father and my martyr
brother's wife are in their hands.
I ran away from them, and I am
going to take refuge in Osman Bey.
I know that valiant Osman Bey...
...will not leave my father alone with his fate.
Who is your father?
Who are you?
I am Akbasli Gunduz Bey's daughter.
From Kayi tribe, Hayme Ana's family...
...Efendize Elcim Hatun.
Father...
This Hatun killed our Alps.
She is lying to save her life.
They were not your Alps!
Go and check them.
My Bey. She is telling the truth.
They are Mongol dogs.
Who are you?
Osman Bey is standing right in front of you.
Now you know who we are.
Now it is their turn!
Alps!
Aren't you ashamed of drawing your
swords against your brothers, huh?
This woman shed our brothers' blood!
She is a spy!
Give that woman to us!
She killed my Alps!
My Bey, what are you doing?
I will take my
revenge from her first!
Do not rise difficulties.
Give that Hatun to us and go your own way.
Look! Don't take another step!
Don't take another step!
Or I will cut her head off!
I said give that woman to us, Alp
-Apparently...
..you don't know us.
It seems that your anger is stronger.
But...
...I caught this Hatun first.
Therefore, I will take my revenge!
Now... If...
..if you want this Hatun..
...you will drop your swords.
You will drop your swords, not us!
Drop your swords!
Let me go! Let me go!
You dastards! Let me go!
Shut up, Hatun!
Don't take another step!
Drop it, my son.
Drop it.
We are not going to die here for a Hatun.
You are trampling on your morals!
You are turning someone who took
refuge in you over to her enemies!
I told you to shut up, Hatun!
Take the girl.
Come. Come.
Take her.
When have I ever given someone innocent
who took refuge in me to someone else, huh?
My name is Osman Bey.
There is no such thing in
the state I am dreaming of.
Come at me now.
Visit turkision.com for more!